{
    "subject": "resource/Pizza_73",
    "predicate": "ontology/numberOfLocations",
    "object": "89",
    "human_readable": "Pizza 73 has 89 locations.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8938903212547302,
            "question": "Where are Pizza 73 locations found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363959193229675,
            "question": "How many locations does Pizza 73 have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6423819065093994,
            "question": "Do you know anything else about Pizza 73 besides the number of locations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4928637444972992,
            "question": "What is the number of Pizza 73 restaurants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4922812283039093,
            "question": "How does the number of Pizza 73 locations compare to other fast food chains?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46203136444091797,
            "question": "Is Pizza 73 a popular pizza chain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36138391494750977,
            "question": "Is Pizza 73 a small or large restaurant chain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3293636739253998,
            "question": "What type of food does Pizza 73 serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26223263144493103,
            "question": "Are there any other restaurants with a similar number of locations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20568013191223145,
            "question": "What factors might contribute to the success of Pizza 73?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pizza 73 has 89 locations.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4714_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other restaurants with a similar number of locations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4714_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of food does Pizza 73 serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4714_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pizza 73 a small or large restaurant chain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4714_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4714_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Pizza 73 has 89 locations, confirming this fact."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Pizza 73 has 89 locations in Alberta, Saskatchewan, and British Columbia. The additional mention of locations in Yukon does not contradict this statement but simply provides further detail about its geographical reach."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}